Andrew Bean

Greenville, North Carolina, United States



andrewbean34@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/andrew-bean-java

Summary

I love to learn and push myself to try new things. I have an open mind for ideas behind my clients, to work with them and shape their idea into a reality.

Over 5 years of extensive development and learning with Java. Over 3 years of experience using SQL, MySQL, SQLite, and MongoDB. 2 years experience utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript. Undertaking and completing many self-taught projects and applying numerous different API's and libraries. 4+ years working with Linux systems. Debian 7, 8, 9, Ubuntu 14.04, 16.04, 18.04.

Experience



Software Programmer

Fiverr

Oct 2018 - Present (2 years +)

I primarily create game addons/plugins for clients that seek out custom and professional work done in a timely and cost-efficient manner. Clients will contact me and explain what they need in an addon, and I will see if I'm able to make it in the budget and time frame they require.



Dishwasher

The Scullery

Jan 2017 - Present (3 years 9 months +)

- Wash dishes, glassware, pots, or pans, by dishwasher, but primarily by hand.
- Maintain kitchen work areas, equipment, and utensils in clean and orderly condition.
- Organize clean dishes, utensils, and cooking equipment in proper storage areas.
- Sort and remove trash, placing it in designated pickup areas.
- Sweep and scrub floors.



Pharmacy Aides

Kue's Pharmacy

Mar 2015 - Feb 2016 (1 year)

- Greet customers and help them locate merchandise
- Accept prescriptions for filling, gathering, and processing necessary information.
- Operate cash register to process cash or credit sales.
- Answer telephone inquires, referring callers to pharmacist when necessary.
- Receive, store, and inventory supplies and medications, check for out-dated medications, and notify pharmacist when inventory levels are low.

Education



Pitt Community College

Associate of Science - AS, Computer Programming 2016 - 2019

Skills

Java • SQL • JavaScript • Social Media • Eclipse • Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) • Databases • MySQL • SQLite • Microsoft Office